[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Congress"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "Is it inevitable that you will have to sit down, your man, the President and Speaker Boehner and just thrash out a deal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Well, Piers, what is inevitable is that Congress has the responsibility to fund the government, to pass bills, they keep the government open.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House", "Congress"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Why is that not happening between the President and John Boehner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Well, first of all, as the President said he would, he spoke with the Speaker of the House and said he would continue to have conversations with leaders in Congress in the days ahead.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "PERSON": ["John Boehner"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "WRB", "NNPS", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "-- vision which it back plays (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "It is -- we are agnostic when it comes to how Republicans pick their leaders in Congress and the President actually has a good relationship with and likes and enjoys John Boehner's company.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 51, "question": "How does this end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Well, first of all I'd say, \"We're making no demands.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Why can't Republicans just see, sense, realize his law, and move on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "NNPS", "RB", "VB", ",", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Sure, it's the same reason that we were elected as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oklahoma City"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 104, "question": "-- and colonoscopies have higher ratings than you?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Four years ago, I was just a normal American citizen in my area in Oklahoma City and many people came to me and said, \"People like you and people like being around you and you're doing good work here.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sidd Jah"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Sidd?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Congressman, my name is Sidd Jah (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Do you think it's fair that Congress is going to continue to get paid while more than 800,000 government employees are furloughed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "ANKFORD: OK, that's a great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "How much are you being paid say for this week, Congressman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I don't break it down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "-- why should the very people who have caused the shutdown continue to be paid when the victims of the shutdown are not being paid?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "RB", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "No, I would assume we're not on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "That cannot be in America's national interest because this only gets solved when eventually they talk to each other, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "That's right and, Piers, I'm glad you asked and I really encourage everybody to go back and look at the beginning of this year when Speaker Boehner spoke and said that he did not want to have anymore negotiations with the President of the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What is it likely to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, two things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay Carney"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "What about Hallie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I wasn't furious I just thought it was amusing that you asked the Republican Congressman about his salary and acted all in dignity he was getting a salary with Jay Carney the way those press folks who is doing such a permanent (ph) job.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hallie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Arkansas"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Why should they get salaries and this very hardworking young lady be sent home on a spur of a moment with the piece of paper and has no money coming into her family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Some of the congressman, a friend of mine Tom Cotton, the congressman from Arkansas said he was giving up his salary for this period, but it's up to each person to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Why is it a non starter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well, because -- first of all --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 236, "question": "RISTOL: Because it's a law like Piers said, but didn't the President suspend the employer mandate, didn't the President change other parts of the law, shouldn't Congress have the right to say something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "But the President has been open to negotiating this law for the last --", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Isn't that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Does that tell you something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "I don't -- I can't see that it was chaos, you know, there are a lot of people that can do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2011"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNPS", "IN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "How do we get through this on pass at the moment and who really is most to blame?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "RBS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well, the reason that we're trying to get everything done right now is that Obama although he says he's willing to negotiate all the time doesn't even sit down with Republicans until as in 2011 they have the debt ceiling that they run up against.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Who's blaming now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Pretty substantially.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "You're telling me that none of these things would have happened in past times, Grover?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "ORQUIST: Well, OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Grover"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz", "Sara Palin"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Hi my name is Miranda Yaufer (ph) and I'm wondering in light of Ted Cruz' recent comments on Obamacare, what do you see as the implications for the upcoming 2013 gubernatorial elections and the face of the GOP?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Yes, I mean this is an interesting point isn't it, Bill because Ted Cruz has made his march, he's the new male version of Sara Palin with one of the better comparison and which he may take as a compliment, many wouldn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2013"], "ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"], "PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"], "PERSON": ["Chris Christie", "Ted Cruz", "Paul Ryan"], "LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNPS", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "But in terms of his ability to direct the Republican Party right now, he's the guy in the saddle isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Well, if Chris Christie going to get reelected the governor of New Jersey and he is not taking orders form Ted Cruz, and I think Republicans have a very promising field for 2016 with an awful a lot of young senators, governors, congressman like Paul Ryan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "JJS", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "What about America incorporates it and how it moves forward and restores its credibility and its reputation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Well I think first of all, Piers that the place where it needs to restore it's reputation most importantly is in the eyes of the American people.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Thou shalt not speak ill of any fellow Republican?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Well, he invented that when he was running ahead as the favorite.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "This is just random selection of people that gets (inaudible) to watch the show, but how much of this is done to just general dissatisfaction with the American political system?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Well, it's because the Democrats and Republicans have created this corrupt system and they been in charge now for a 150 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "What do you think of Obamacare?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I don't think anything of it, because my belief is quite simple.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "And let's get real for a moment, is it feasible in our lifetime that you could have a candidate running for president who was successful, who was not a member of the Republican or Democratic Party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I did it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Could you do it on a presidential level?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "What is your response?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "My response would be then I guess a real person shouldn't be president because I'm a real person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Yes, because my belief is if you tell the truth, you don't have to have a good memory.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Not new that there may have been a conspiracy to assassinate, what is new about your book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Well, what's new about our book is there's always new information coming out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WP"], "qSentId": 507, "question": "So, who -- And who killed Kennedy, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", ":", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Yes, you can't answer that question because it's been 50 years and there's nowhere -- no way to say specifically who", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Jesse, here's my point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Now, why do you know more than he does?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Well, because of the fact, there's a whole lot of information.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Secret Service"], "LOCATION": ["Kennedy", "Texas"]}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Oh, come on, who do you think did it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "The Secret Service protected Kennedy more after death and they did when was alive because they illegally took the body out of Texas.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Jesse, who do you think kills JFK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "There is multiple choices.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse"], "LOCATION": ["JFK"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "You've written the book about it, well what do you think is the most likely theory?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "ENTURA: I think -- Here's the deal, there were two conspiracies that took place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131001pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "You think you've won the argument simply because I can't name who did it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]